Guide to the Gay Cable Network Archives, 1982-2001 MSS.231
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XI: Gay USA
  - 1998 Vol. XVI
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 17 [Air date: 4/23/1998], April 1998; ID: 231.0065 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0065)
      5. Interview: Gary Mallon, Executive Director of Green Chimneys, discusses LGBT youth homelessness.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 18 [Air Date: 4/30/1998], April 1998; ID: 231.0066 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0066)
      2. Footage of Reggie White on ABC's 20/20 regarding his controversial comments on homosexuality.
      4. Entertainment, includes special celebration for Ann Northrop's 50th birthday.
      5. Andrew Taines interviews Scott Dobbins, Co-Executive Producer of the Out on the Edge Together Festival, regarding the festival.
      6. Interview: Marvin Schwam, of Gay Entertainment Television (GET), discusses GET's going public.
      7. Nora Burns discusses recent nightlife and entertainment-related events that relate to the LGBT community.
      8. Interview: Terry Kaelber, Executive Director of Senior Action in a Gay Environment (SAGE), and Madelin Alk, Vice President of SAGE, discuss the first national conference on aging in the LGBT community.
      9. Footage of Walter Schubert, CEO of the Gay Financial Network (GFN), speaking at the Launch Party for GFN.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 19 [Air date: 5/7/1998], May 1998; ID: 231.0067 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0067)
      2. Interview: Carren Strock, author, discusses her book "Married Women Who Love Women".
      4. Lou Maletta interviews Brian Sloan, director, regarding his film "I Think I Do". Includes film footage.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 20 [Air date: 5/14/1998], May 1998; ID: 231.0068 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0068)
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 21 [Air date: 5/21/1998], May 1998; ID: 231.0577 (Box 37, Media ID: 231.0577)
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 22 [Air date: 5/28/1998], May 1998; ID: 231.0069 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0069)
      2. Footage from NY1 of Cardinal John Joseph O'Connor denouncing proposed domestic partner benefits legislation.
      3. Interview: Steve Ault and Leslie Cagan, activists, discuss the Millennium March on Washington.
      COMMERCIAL: National AIDS Hotline, "Protect your kids from AIDS. Talk with them about sex".
      COMMERCIAL: National AIDS Hotline, "Isn't it time you talked with your kids?" Features Kerry Carson, activist.
      5. Interview: Dennis Beauchemin, victim of bias crime, discusses his assault.
      COMMERCIAL: National AIDS Hotline, "Carry the torch. Talk about AIDS."
      COMMERCIAL: National AIDS Hotline, "Make the effort. Talk about sex. Protect your kids from AIDS".
      7. Footage from the 20th Annual International Mr. Leather contest.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 23 [Air date: 6/4/1998], June 1998; ID: 231.0070 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0070)
      COMMERCIAL: Sierra Club
      3. Lou Maletta interviews Guy Kettelhack, author, regarding his book "Easing the Ache"
      5. Footage of Earvin 'Magic' Johnson, basketball player, on The Rosie O'Donnell Show discussing his new talk show.
      6. Nora Burns discusses recent nightlife and entertainment-related events that relate to the LGBT community.
      7. Footage of Kate Clinton, comedian, on The Rosie O'Donnell Show discussing her personal life.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 24 [Air date: 6/11/1998], June 1998; ID: 231.0578 (Box 37, Media ID: 231.0578)
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 25 [Air date: 6/18/1998], June 1998; ID: 231.0071 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0071)
      3. Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund presents "The Lambda Update", with Kevin Cathcart, Executive Director, and John Scarborough, Staff Attorney, Southern Regional Office.
      5. Andrew Taines discusses entertainment-related events.
      7. Interview: Paul Harris, playwright, and Patrick [Lloyd], director, discuss their play "To Have and To Hold".
      8. Lou Maletta interviews John Weis, chairman of Gay-Male-S/M Activists (GMSMA), regarding the Folsom Street East block party.
      9. Clip from "In the Life" show, "American as Apple Pie" episode
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 26 [Air date: 6/25/1998], June 1998; ID: 231.0072 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0072)
      3. Footage of Peter Vallone, Speaker of NYC Council; Alan Hevesi, NYC Comptroller; Deborah Glick, NYS Assembly member; and Kate Clinton, comedian, at the 15th Annual Center Garden Party
      4. Footage of Pride Rally, including speech by Margarita Lopez, NYC Council Member.
      5. Footage of the Gay Officers Action League's "Heritage of Courage Celebration"
      6. Footage of Folsom Street East II
      7. Footage of the Mr. LURE Contest
      8. Interview with Christopher Lynn, NYC politician.
      9. Entertainment, includes Nora Burns discussing recent nightlife and entertainment-related events that relate to the LGBT community.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 27 [Air date: 7/2/1998], July 1998; ID: 231.0073 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0073)
      2. Footage from CSPAN regarding the "Legal Age of Homosexual Consent" in the United Kingdom.
      3. Footage of Pride Month event in which Mark Green, [politician], honors activists at City Hall. Includes footage of Harry Bartel and Brian Landeche, owners of Splash bar; Craig Lucas, playwright; and Betty Santoro, member of Lesbian Feminist Liberation.
      4. Footage of activists protesting the mayor's participation in the Lesbian and Gay Pride March.
      6. Interview: James LaRocca, candidate for the Democratic primary for Governor of New York, discusses his political platform with respect to LGBT issues.
      7. Footage of Tom of Finland at the Manhunt Party.
      8. Nora Burns discusses recent nightlife and entertainment-related events that relate to the LGBT community.
      9. Entertainment
      10. Footage of the 1998 Gay and Lesbian Pride Parade. Includes footage of NYC politicians Margarita Lopez, Peter Vallone, Rudy Giuliani, Alan Hevesi, and Mark Green.
      11. Footage of Pier Dance.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 28 [Air date: 7/9/1998], July 1998; ID: 231.0074 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0074)
      1. Andy Humm and Frank Jump discuss recent general events that relate to the LGBT community.
      2. Interview: James LaRocca, candidate for the Democratic primary for Governor of New York, discusses his political platform with respect to LGBT issues.
      4. Interview: Dennis Hensley, author, discusses his book "Misadventures in the (213)".
      6. Lou Maletta interviews Louise Rafkin, author, regarding her book "Other People's Dirt: A Housecleaner's Curious Adventures".
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 29 [Air date: 7/16/1998], July 1998; ID: 231.0075 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0075)
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 30 [Air date: 7/23/1998], July 1998; ID: 231.0076 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0076)
      Program content: [Callen-Lorde]
      2. Interview: Paula Ettelbrick, veteran activist, discusses the upcoming national event Equality Begins at Home.
      4. Callen - Lorde Community Health Center Update.
      5. Nora Burns interviews Jeffrey, Jeff, and Lance, members of the New York Express gay basketball team.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 31 [Air date: 7/30/1998], July 1998; ID: 231.0077 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0077)
      2. Interview: Laura Moore, Gay Games Figure Skater, discusses the upcoming fifth Gay Games in Amsterdam.
      4. Interview: Michael Shernoff, editor, discusses his book "Gay Widowers: Life After the Death of a Partner".
      5. Interview: Stanley Bojarski and Michael West, cast members, discuss the musical "Howard Crabtree's When Pigs Fly". Includes performance footage.
      COMMERCIAL: Cable Positive, PSA for AIDS information
      8. Additional footage of "Howard Crabtree's When Pigs Fly".
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 32 [Air date: 8/6/1998], August 1998; ID: 231.0078 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0078)
      2. Footage from CSPAN of Nancy Pelosi, Democratic Representative for the House of Representatives, regarding "Domestic Partners and Employees Benefits" legislation.
      3. Footage from NY1 of US Senate press conference. Includes footage of politicians Betsy McCaughey Ross, Margarita Lopez, James Larocca, Geraldine Ferraro, and Alan Hevesi, and activist Andy Humm.
      4. Footage from News at Ten of the Gay Games at Amsterdam.
      6. Interview: Joe Calarco, production adapter and director, discusses his all-male play "Shakespeare's R & J". Includes performance footage.
      7. Callen - Lorde Community Health Center Update.
      8. Entertainment
      9. Interview: Arthur Hanket, playwright and actor, discusses his solo play "Saint Genet: Language of the Wall". Includes performance footage.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 33 [Air date: 8/13/1998], August 1998; ID: 231.0079 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0079)
      1. Andy Humm and Barbara Raab discuss recent general events that relate to the LGBT community.
      2. Interview: Mitchell Anderson, actor, discusses "Visiting Mr. Green", a play in which he stars.
      5. Andrew Taines interviews Jeff Krell, author, and Craig Dawson, actor, regarding Krell's comic strip "Jayson" and its stage production.
      6. Lou Maletta interviews Alvino Najar, artist and sculptor, regarding his artwork and personal life.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 34 [Air date: 8/20/1998], August 1998; ID: 231.0080 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0080)
      3. Footage of Andy Humm interviewing Clyde Rabideau, Mayor of Plattsburgh, NY, and Candidate for Lieutenant Governor of NY State, regarding his political platform.
      5. Lou Maletta interviews Ren Volpe, author, regarding her book "The Lady Mechanic's Total Car Care for the Clueless: A Manual for Car Owners".
      6. Footage of the 16th Annual GMHC (Gay Men's Health Crisis) Morning Party on Fire Island. Includes footage of Lou Maletta interviewing partygoers.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 36 [Air date: 9/3/1998], September 1998; ID: 231.0082 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0082)
      3. Lou Maletta interviews Mike Parker, artist, regarding his Disney and entertainment-inspired paintings.
      5. Footage of Ryan Phillippe as gay teenager Billy on the soap opera "One Life to Live".
      6. Footage of "The Queen's Cantonese Conversational Course" video from the Leslie-Lohman Gay Art Foundation's Homoerotic Video Trash II. Introduced by Lou Maletta.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 37 [Air date: 9/10/1998], September 1998; ID: 231.0083 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0083)
      2. Interview: Tom Duane, NYC Council Member, discusses recent crimes against the LGBT community.
      5. Footage of Wigstock '98. Includes footage of Lou Maletta interviewing attendees.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 38 [Air date: 9/17/1998], September 1998; ID: 231.0084 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0084)
      1. Interview: Matt Foreman, Executive Director of the Empire State Pride Agenda, discusses the recent election results and their effects on the LGBT community.
      6. Lou Maletta interviews Arch Brown, playwright, regarding his play "Freeze!". Includes performance footage.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 39 [Air date: 9/24/1998], September 1998; ID: 231.0085 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0085)
      2. Interview: Sergeant Edgar Rodriguez, President of the Gay Officers Action League (GOAL), discusses police department events and recent crimes against the LGBT community.
      5. Lou Maletta interviews Miss Naomi, author, regarding her book "Forbidden Art: The World of Erotica". COMMERCIAL: Lesbian and Gay Public Awareness Project, tells the story of Bobby Griffith
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 40 [Air date: 10/1/1998], October 1998; ID: 231.0086 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0086)
      4. Lou Maletta interviews Barry Wyatt, actor, regarding his personal life and his acting role in the film "Skin & Bone". Includes film footage.
      COMMERCIAL: The New Ramrod Showplace
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 41 [Air date: 10/1/1998], October 1998; ID: 231.0087 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0087)
      1. Footage of Virginia Apuzzo, [activist], and Al Gore, US Vice President, speaking at the Empire State Pride Agenda Awards Dinner. Includes footage of Andy Humm interviewing attendees.
      5. Interview: Dan Savage, Sex Advice Columnist, discusses his book "Savage Love".
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 42 [Air date: 10/15/1998], October 1998; ID: 231.0579 (Box 37, Media ID: 231.0579)
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 42 [Air date: 10/15/1998] [Empty], October 1998; ID: 231.0489 (Box 31, Media ID: 231.0489)
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 43 [Air date: 10/22/1998], October 1998; ID: 231.0088 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0088)
      2. Interview: Suzy Lee Korn, organizer of New York protest, discusses the recent rally to protest the killing of Matthew Shepard.
      4. Interview: Katherine Acey, Executive Director of the ASTREA National Lesbian Action Foundation, discusses the organization's turning 20 years old.
      5. Interview: [Sean] discusses the play "Corpus Christi" by Terrence McNally.
      6. Lou Maletta interviews Roland Tec, writer and director, and Paul [Outlaw], actor, regarding Tec's film "All the Rage". Includes film footage.
      7. Footage of the Peace March for Matthew Shepard. Includes footage of Lou Maletta and Andy Humm at the event.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 44 [Air date: 10/29/1998], October 1998; ID: 231.0089 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0089)
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 45 [Air date: 11/5/1998], November 1998; ID: 231.0090 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0090)
      2. Interview: Tim Sweeney, Deputy Director of the Empire State Pride Agenda, discusses political issues that affect the LGBT community.
      5. Interview: Jay Corcoran, director, discusses his film "Undetectable" following three men and three women taking protease [inhibitors] to combat HIV. Includes film footage.
      6. Peter Sparrow interviews Ron Athey, performance artist, regarding the documentary "Hallelujah! Ron Athey: A Story of Deliverance". Includes film trailer.
      7. Additional footage of Jay Corcoran's film "Undetectable".
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 46 [Air date: 11/12/1998], November 1998; ID: 231.0091 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0091)
      2. Footage of Andy Humm for Marriage Equality at Same Sex Marriage Rally. Includes footage of Evan Wolfson, of Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund; Dick Gottfried, of the NYS Assembly; Kathryn Freed, of the NYC Council; Tim Sweeney, of the Empire State Pride Agenda; Patty Penalosa, of Marriage Equality; Kevin McGruder, Gay Men of African Descent, Rabbi Sharon Kleinbaum, of the [Lesbian and Gay] Synagogue; John Magisano, of the Metropolitan Community Church; and Joe DeFilippis, [activist].
      5. Interview: Deian McBryde, entertainer, regarding his personal life and artistic work. Includes McBryde performing "I'll Be True to You" from his CD "Mollyboy".
      6. Interview: Paul Wirhun, artist, discusses his artistic egg designs.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 47 [Air date: 11/19/1998], November 1998; ID: 231.0092 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0092)
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 48 [Air date: 11/26/1998], November 1998; ID: 231.0093 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0093)
      COMMERCIAL: Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC), information for businesses regarding HIV/AIDS
      3. Interview: Suzanne Goldberg, Staff Attorney for Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund, discusses the repeal of the sodomy law in Georgia.
      4. Interview: Hugh Hysell, director, and Ken Mason, actor, discuss the all-male play adaptation of "The Importance of Being Earnest".
      5. Interview: Eric Bernat, actor, and David Drake, director, discuss their show "Starstruck". Includes performance footage.
      7. Gallery Performance by Ron Athey
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 49 [Air date: 12/3/1998], December 1998; ID: 231.0094 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0094)
      2. Interview: Evan Wolfson, of the Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund, discusses the same-sex marriage case in Hawaii.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 50 [Air date: 12/10/1998], December 1998; ID: 231.0095 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0095)
      3. Michael Russell, Ph.D., child psychologist and psychotherapist, discusses preparing children for the holidays.
      6. Andy Humm and Ann Northrop wish Lou Maletta a happy 62nd birthday. Includes clip of George Michael's music video for his single "Outside".
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 51 [Air date: 12/17/1998], December 1998; ID: 231.0096 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0096)
      2. Interview: Tom Duane, NYS Senator Elect, discusses political issues that affect the LGBT community.
      4. Interview: Dr. Allan Frank, Home Access Health Corporation, discusses the AIDS Home Test.
      5. Interview: Gean Harwood, author, discusses his book "The Oldest Gay Couple in America: A 70-Year Journey Through Same-Sex America".
      7. Nora Burns discusses recent entertainment-related events that relate to the LGBT community.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 52 [Air date: 12/24/1998], December 1998; ID: 231.0001 (Box 1, Media ID: 231.0001)
      2. Interview: Troy Masters, LGNY publisher, discusses his enrollment in first AIDS vaccine trial in U.S.
      5. Interview: William Bland & George Bellinger, Jr., activists, regarding AIDS in the African American community.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 53 [Air date: 12/31/1998], December 1998; ID: 231.0097 (Box 7, Media ID: 231.0097)
      1. "A Year in Review": Andy Humm, TV Producer Barbara Raab, NYC Council member Phil Reed, and Ann Northrop review events from 1998 that were significant to the LGBT community.
  - 1999 Vol. XVII
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVII, Episode No. 1 [Air date: 1/7/1999], January 1999; ID: 231.0580 (Box 37, Media ID: 231.0580)
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVII, Episode No. 2 [Air date: 1/14/1999], January 1999; ID: 231.0002 (Box 1, Media ID: 231.0002)
      2. Footage from when GCN broke the story about Prince Edward being gay in 1993.
      3. Interview: Tim Sweeney, of Empire State Pride Agenda, discusses the first legislation in New York regarding sexual orientation.
      5. Entertainment, includes interview with Rafael Risemberg, founder of Date Bait, regarding his connection service for gay men, lesbians, and non-gay people.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVII, Episode No. 3 [Air date: 1/21/1999], January 1999; ID: 231.0003 (Box 1, Media ID: 231.0003)
      2. Footage from Bill Clinton's State of the Union address.
      3. Interview: David Pumo, of the Urban Justice Center, discusses the lawsuit suing the city and state of New York on behalf of LGBT foster children.
      6. Lou Maletta interviews Wayne Hoffman, co-editor of "Policing Public Sex," regarding his book. Footage from GCN program Static.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVII, Episode No. 4 [Air date: 1/28/1999], January 1999; ID: 231.0004 (Box 1, Media ID: 231.0004)
      2. Interview: Christopher Lynn, City Council Candidate for 3rd Council District of Manhattan, discusses his political platform.
      4. Interview: Kate Clinton, actress, discusses her one-lesbian show "Correct Me If I'm Right." Includes performance footage.
      5. Entertainment, includes interview with Charles Busch, writer and actor, regarding his new play "Shanghai Moon."
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVII, Episode No. 5 [Air date: 2/4/1999], February 1999; ID: 231.0005 (Box 1, Media ID: 231.0005)
      2. Interview: Aubrey Lees, City Council Candidate for 3rd Council District of Manhattan, discusses her political platform.
      3. AIDS News, including interview with Robert Hagerty, Study Coordinator, and Andrew Smith, Vaccine Volunteer, discuss the VaxGen Trial for AIDS research.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVII, Episode No. 6 [Air date: 2/11/1999], February 1999; ID: 231.0006 (Box 1, Media ID: 231.0006)
      2. Footage regarding assault on Dan Eaton by six New York City cops.
      3. Interview: Christine Quinn, City Council Candidate for 3rd Council District of Manhattan, discusses her political platform.
      5. Entertainment, including interview: Kirsten Sahs, actress, and Jonathan Harvey, author, discuss the play production of "Beautiful Thing." Includes performance footage.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVII, Episode No. 7 [Air date: 2/18/1999], February 1999; ID: 231.0007 (Box 1, Media ID: 231.0007)
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVII, Episode No. 8 [Air date: 2/25/1999], February 1999; ID: 231.0008 (Box 1, Media ID: 231.0008)
      COMMERCIAL: "Do You Have IRS Problems?", Jack L. Hollander, Attorney at Law, NYC
      4. Lou Maletta interviews Frank Stasio, of Empire State Pride Agenda, regarding the upcoming Eleventh Annual Night of 100 Parties at Grand Central Terminal
      COMMERCIAL: "Stop Suffering From IRS Problems!", Jack L. Hollander, Attorney at Law, NYC
      6. Clip from Leeza talk show– Interview with Tracey Ullman
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVII, Episode No. 9 [Air date: 3/4/1999], March 1999; ID: 231.0009 (Box 1, Media ID: 231.0009)
      2. Interview: Patty Penalosa, co-Chair of Marriage Equality, discusses same-sex marriage.
      5. Lou Maletta interviews Mitchell Anderson, actor, regarding the film "Relax…It's Just Sex". Includes film footage.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVII, Episode No. 10 [Air date: 3/11/1999], March 1999; ID: 231.0010 (Box 1, Media ID: 231.0010)
      1. Barbara Raab and Ann Northrop discuss recent general events that relate to the LGBT community.
      2. Interview: Karla Jay, author, discusses her new book "Tales of the Lavender Menace".
      4. Entertainment, includes footage of Andy Humm interviewing Rex Reed, NYS Senator Tom Duane, and City Council Member Christine Quinn, Sir Ian McKellen, and Michael Musto, regarding the upcoming Academy Awards and LGBT entertainment-related events.
      5. Footage of Lou Maletta at Empire State Pride Agenda's Night of 100 Parties at Grand Central Terminal.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVII, Episode No. 11 [Air date: 3/18/1999], March 1999; ID: 231.0011 (Box 1, Media ID: 231.0011)
      2. Footage from coverage of the Irish Gay and Lesbian Organization protest regarding the exclusion of gays and lesbians from the St. Patrick's Day parade. Includes interview with Christine Quinn.
      4. Interview: David Marshall Grant, playwright, regarding his newly produced play "Snakebit".
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVII, Episode No. 12 [Air date: 3/25/1999], March 1999; ID: 231.0012 (Box 1, Media ID: 231.0012)
      2. Interview: Barbara Smith, author, discusses her new book "The Truth That Never Hurts".
      4. Interview: Daniel Scott, Producing Director of The MorganScott Ballet, discusses the new performance "Remembering Matthew Shepard: A Vigil in Dance". Includes performance footage.
      5. Entertainment, includes footage of Sir Ian McKellen's winning the Independent Spirit Award for Best Male Lead.
      6. Interview: Jean-Claude van Itallie, playwright and actor, discusses his new play "War, Sex and Dreams". Includes footage.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVII, Episode No. 13 [Air date: 4/1/1999], April 1999; ID: 231.0013 (Box 1, Media ID: 231.0013)
      2. Lou Maletta interviews Mark Elderkin, Founder of Gay.com, and Andrew Cramer, CEO of Gay.com, regarding the benefits of their website.
      4. Andrew Taines discusses the London theatre scene.
      5. Interview: Jean-Claude van Itallie, playwright and actor, discusses his new play "War, Sex and Dreams".
      COMMERCIAL: "AIDS. It's your business." CDC, Business Responds to AIDS
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVII, Episode No. 14 [Air date: 4/8/1999], April 1999; ID: 231.0014 (Box 1, Media ID: 231.0014)
      COMMERCIAL: "Justice & Reconciliation" event regarding police brutality, New Yorkers for Law, Order Peace & Justice
      2. Interview: Minnie Bruce Pratt, poet, and Katherine Acey, Executive Director of the Astraea National Lesbian Action Foundation, discuss Pratt's new poetry book "Walking Back Up Depot Street" and the Astraea Foundation's Lesbian Writers Fund Gala.